Guide to the Records of Athletics Programs at New York University RG.41
New York University Archives
- RG 41.10: NYU Olympic Athletes
  NYU athletes have been competing in the Olympics since 1904. Between that year and 1988, 19 athletes from NYU have won a total of 28 medals.
  Fencing and track have generated the most Olympians from NYU. In 1988 an exhibition was created to highlight the successes of NYU's Olympic athletes.
  This series is comprised of materials relating to the NYU Olympic athletes from 1904-1988, including rosters and biographies of these athletes as well as material from a 1988 exhibition on NYU athletes who have competed in the Olympics.
  - NYU Olympians: Exhibit Correspondence and Captions, 1988-1990; cuid15537 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, Cliff Bertrand, 1988; cuid15538 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - NYU Olympic Exhibit, 1988; cuid15539 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - NYU Olympian Booklet, cuid15540 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Penn State at the Olympics (A model booklet), 1988; cuid15541 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Chronology, no date; cuid15542 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - NYU Panam Games Athletics, undated; cuid15543 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Statistics of Participants, undated; cuid15544 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Team Member Listing/Addresses, 1988; cuid15545 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Listed by Sport/Event, undated; cuid15546 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Info on NYU Olympians, 1987; cuid15547 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - 1904 Team, undated; cuid15548 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - 1912 Team, undated; cuid15549 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - 1920 Team, undated; cuid15550 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - 1924 Team, undated; cuid15551 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - 1928 Team, undated; cuid15552 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - 1932 Team, undated; cuid15553 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - 1934 Track Team, undated; cuid15554 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - 1936 Team, undated; cuid15555 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - 1940 Team, undated; cuid15556 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - 1948 Team, undated; cuid15557 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - 1952 Team, cuid15558 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - 1956 Team, cuid15559 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - 1960 Team, undated; cuid15560 (Box 46, File 24)
  - 1964 Team, undated; cuid15561 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - 1968 Team, undated; cuid15562 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - 1972 Team, undated; cuid15563 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - 1976 Team, undated; cuid15564 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - 1980 Team, undated; cuid15565 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - 1984 Team, undated; cuid15566 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - 1988 Team, cuid15567 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Addresses for NYU Olympians, undated; cuid15568 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Millrose Games, 1989; cuid15569 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Apostol, Paul, undated; cuid15570 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Armitage, Norman, undated; cuid15571 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Baird, George, undated; cuid15572 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Ballinger, Ed, undated; cuid15573 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Becker, Benjamin, undated; cuid15574 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Bertrand, Cliff, undated; cuid15575 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Byrnes, Joseph, undated; cuid15576 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Calarese, Wladimiro, undated; cuid15577 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Cann, Howard, undated; cuid15578 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Carnevale, Bernard, undated; cuid15579 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Castello, Hugo, undated; cuid15580 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Castro, Frank, undated; cuid15581 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Checkes, Jeffrey, undated; cuid15582 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Cohen, Herbert, undated; cuid15583 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Conwell, Edward, undated; cuid15584 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Corbitt, Ted, undated; cuid15585 (Box 47, File 16)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Cumiskey, Frank, undated; cuid15586 (Box 47, File 17)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Cunningham, Glenn, undated; cuid15587 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Dasaro, Mike, undated; cuid15588 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Davis, Martin, undated; cuid15589 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: de Caprilles, Jose, undated; cuid15590 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: de Capriles Miguel, undated; cuid15591 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Denman, Elliot, undated; cuid15592 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Dickson, Gordon, undated; cuid15593 (Box 47, File 24)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Dow, Robert, undated; cuid15594 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Dyce, Byron, undated; cuid15595 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Edwards, Philip, cuid15596 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Ellis, Larry, undated; cuid15597 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Engel, Martin, undated; cuid15598 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Feurbach, Leon, undated; cuid15599 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Frontera, Jim, undated; cuid15600 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Furth, Sol, undated; cuid15601 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Giolito, Silvio, undated; cuid15602 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Glazer, Gene, undated; cuid15603 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Griffin, Jack, undated; cuid15604 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Gubner, Gary, undated; cuid15605 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Guira, John, undated; cuid15606 (Box 47, Folder data_value_missing_445b108d567aca6227ac2a32691e04b7)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Hammon, Graeme, undated; cuid15607 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Healey, Joseph, undated; cuid15608 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Heiss, Carol, undated; cuid15609 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Hurme, Risto, undated; cuid15610 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Jones, Gilbert, undated; cuid15611 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Jones, Samuel, undated; cuid15612 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Kaplan, Steve, undated; cuid15613 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Keane, Jack, undated; cuid15614 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Lang, Martin, undated; cuid15615 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Lapp, Bernice, undated; cuid15616 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Lewis, Norman, undated; cuid15617 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Lindstrom, Lisa, undated; cuid15618 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Lofton, Michael, undated; cuid15619 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Lumpp, Ray, undated; cuid15620 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: MacDonald, Bruce, undated; cuid15621 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Macknowski, Steve, undated; cuid15622 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Mason, George, undated; cuid15623 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Master, Edith, undated; cuid15624 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: McGary, Ethel, undated; cuid15625 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: McKenzie, Gordon, undated; cuid15626 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: McSheehy, Jones, undated; cuid15627 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Mondschein, Irving, undated; cuid15628 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Moore, Roy, undated; cuid15629 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Mormando, Steve, undated; cuid15630 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Novick, Dean, undated; cuid15631 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Ornstein, Charles, undated; cuid15632 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Park, Dong Keun, undated; cuid15633 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Pearman, Reginald, undated; cuid15634 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Pechinsky, Sally, undated; cuid15635 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Peterson, Gus, undated; cuid15636 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Pinkasov, Seymon, undated; cuid15637 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Poprata, Dolph, undated; cuid15638 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Prokop, Austin, undated; cuid15639 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Rossini, Lou, undated; cuid15640 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Scandurra, Aldo, undated; cuid15641 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Schoolman, Irving, undated; cuid15642 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Scrobe, Edward, undated; cuid15643 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Sieja, Stanley, unknown; cuid15644 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Spitz, George, undated; cuid15645 (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Stone, Donna, undated; cuid15646 (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Toussant, Cheryl, undated; cuid15647 (Box 48, Folder 37)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Voliva, Richard, undated; cuid15648 (Box 48, Folder 38)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Von Elling, Emil, undated; cuid15649 (Box 48, Folder 39)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Walker, Leroy, undated; cuid15650 (Box 48, Folder 40)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Walker, Stuart, undated; cuid15651 (Box 48, Folder 41)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Walz, Allen, undated; cuid15652 (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Washburn, Mary, undated; cuid15653 (Box 48, Folder 43)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Weber, Jake, undated; cuid15654 (Box 48, Folder 44)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Wedderburn, Jimmy, undated; cuid15655 (Box 48, Folder 45)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Westbrook, Peter, undated; cuid15656 (Box 48, Folder 46)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: White, Ruth, undated; cuid15657 (Box 48, Folder 47)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Wieselgren, Hans, undated; cuid15658 (Box 48, Folder 48)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Witzk, Herman, undated; cuid15659 (Box 48, Folder 49)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Woodruff, John, undated; cuid15660 (Box 48, Folder 50)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Zaremba, Peter, undated; cuid15661 (Box 48, Folder 51)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Zuaro, Vincent, undated; cuid15662 (Box 48, Folder 52)
- RG 41.11: Tennis, 1919-1976
  History of Tennis at NYU
  Men's tennis gained varsity status in 1907 and the first squad consisted only of four players. From the 1919 to 1927 seasons the men competed without a coach. During the 1930s the men's team consistently made the New York State Intercollegiate Championships. Men's tennis is strictly a spring sport.
  Women's tennis started at NYU in the late 1920s. The team played only in the spring until 1973, when they added fall competition.
  Men's and women's tennis teams continue to compete at the Division III level.
  Series 41.11 contains the records pertaining to the tennis team. Men's tennis began at NYU in 1907, and women's tennis began in 1923. The records within this series range from 1919-1976 and contain tennis records, rosters, schedules, press releases, and clippings.
  Men's and women's tennis results for 1983-2014 are located in Archives H.
  - Tennis All-Time Records, 1919-1955; cuid15663 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Tennis Schedules, 1945-1946; cuid15664 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Tennis Schedules, 1946-1947; cuid15665 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Tennis Roster and Press Releases, 1948; cuid15666 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Tennis Press Information, 1950; cuid15667 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Tennis Press Information, 1952; cuid15668 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Tennis Correspondence, 1954-1955; cuid15669 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Tennis Schedule, 1956-1957; cuid15670 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Tennis Press Information, 1958-1962; cuid15671 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Tennis Clipping, 1963; cuid15672 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Tennis Press Information and Clippings, 1964; cuid15673 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Tennis Press Information and Clippings, 1965; cuid15674 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Tennis Press Information and Clippings, 1966; cuid15675 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Tennis Press Information and Clippings, 1967; cuid15676 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Tennis Press Information and Clippings, 1968; cuid15677 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Tennis Press Information, 1969; cuid15678 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Tennis Press Information and Clippings, 1970; cuid15679 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Tennis Press Information and Clippings, 1970-1971; cuid15680 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Tennis Clippings, 1971; cuid15681 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Tennis Press Information and Clippings, 1975-1976; cuid15682 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Emerson, Gerald Biography, 1937-1939; cuid15683 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Henriquez, Carlos Biography, 1949; cuid15684 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Kurtz, Earl Biography, 1965; cuid15685 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- RG 41.12: Golf, 1930-1976
  History of Golf at NYU
  Golf became a varsity sport at NYU in 1930. Just nine years later, however, the team was dissolved. When it returned in 1954, the men went undefeated with victories over city rivals Manhattan College, St. John's University, and Columbia University. In the 1980s, the team used Riverdale Country Club in New Jersey for its home matches. The team competes at the Division III level in the University Athletic Association conference.
  Women's golf arrived at NYU in 2007.
  Men's golf results for 2000-2014 can be found in Archives H. Women's golf results for 2007-2014 can be found in Archives H.
  The golf team was started at New York University in 1930. The records for this team span 1930 to 1976 and contain player biographies, newspaper clippings, golf tournament programs, and NYU press releases.
  - Golf Metropolitan Championships, 1963; cuid15686 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Golf Press Information and Team Records, 1954; cuid15687 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Golf Press Information and Golf, 1956-1962; cuid15688 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Golf Press Information, 1963; cuid15689 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Golf Clippings and Press Information, 1964; cuid15690 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Golf Clippings and Press Information, 1965; cuid15691 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Golf Clippings and Press Information, 1966; cuid15692 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Golf Clippings and Press Information, 1967; cuid15693 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Golf Clippings and Press Information, 1968; cuid15694 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Golf Clippings and Press Information, 1969; cuid15695 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Golf Clippings and Press Information, 1969; cuid15696 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Golf Clippings and Press Information, 1970; cuid15697 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Golf Clippings and Press Information, 1970; cuid15698 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Golf Press Information, 1972; cuid15699 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Golf Team Equipment Record, 1973; cuid15700 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Pechar, Stanley Biography, 1960; cuid15701 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Penzetti, Al Biography, 1957; cuid15702 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Reissman, Jeff Biograph, 1972; cuid15703 (Box 43, Folder 40)
- RG 41.13: Soccer, 1958-1973
  History of Soccer at NYU
  Soccer arrived at NYU in 1923 and was called "soccer football." The 1923 team had a winning season despite a lack of funds and a field on which to practice. In 1926, the program was terminated but returned in 1958 in an informal capacity. The team went undefeated in its first year back under the leadership of Coach Allan Towbin. Soccer returned to varsity status in 1959. The NYU soccer team continues to compete on the varsity level for both men and women in the University Athletics Association Conference.
  Series 41.13 is comprised of the records of the soccer team, including newspaper clippings, press information, team rosters, and player biographies ranging in date from 1958 to 1973. There is also some documentation from the initial iteration of the team in the 1920s.
  Men's soccer results for 1983-2014 can be found in Archives H. Women's soccer results for 1995-2014 can be found in Archives H.
  - Soccer, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Soccer Records, 1922-1967; cuid15704 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Freshman Soccer Results, 1959-1966; cuid15705 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Varsity Soccer Results, 1922-1926; cuid15706 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Soccer Club Records, 1958; cuid15707 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Soccer Press Information, 1959; cuid15708 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Soccer Clippings and Press Information, 1960; cuid15709 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Soccer Team Rosters, Press Information, and Clippings, 1961; cuid15710 (Box 44, Folder 1961)
  - Soccer Clippings and Press Information, 1962; cuid15711 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Soccer Clippings and Press Information, 1963; cuid15712 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Soccer Team Rosters, Press Information, and Clippings, 1964; cuid15713 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Soccer Clippings and Press Information, 1965; cuid15714 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Soccer Clippings, Press Information, and Awards, 1966; cuid15715 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Soccer Clippings and Press Information, 1967; cuid15716 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Soccer Clippings and Press Information, 1968; cuid15717 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Soccer Clippings and Press Information, 1969; cuid15718 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Soccer Clippings and Press Information, 1970; cuid15719 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Soccer Clippings and Press Information, 1971; cuid15720 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Soccer Clippings and Press Information, 1972; cuid15721 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Soccer, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Gestal, Robin Biography, 1972; cuid15722 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Killian, Frederick Biography, 1964; cuid15723 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Kish, Andrew Biograph, 1965-1968; cuid15724 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Larrea, Robert Biography, 1967; cuid15725 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Messing, Shep Biography, 1968-1969; cuid15726 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Ramirez, Arnold Biography, 1972; cuid15727 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Rossabi, Mayer Biography, 1962-1963; cuid15728 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Stover, James Biography, 1968; cuid15729 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Towbin, Allen Biography, 1958-1961; cuid15730 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Vargas, George Biography, 1964-1972; cuid15731 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Yellows Soccer, 1973; cuid15732 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- RG 41.14: Cross-Country, cuid15733
  Series 41.13 is comprised of the records of the Cross-Country Team
- RG 41.16: Swimming
  History of Swimming at NYU
  Men's and women's swimming became varsity sports in the 1920s. Swim meets were held at the University Heights campus until its closure in 1973. When the Coles Sport Center was completed in 1981, the teams had a new home near Washington Square. Both teams have had numerous winning seasons throughout the years and have produced a number of Olympians. The men's and women's swimming teams continue to compete at the Division III level of the NCAA.
  Series 41.13 is comprised of the records of the Swim Team.
  - Women's Swimming, 1945-1947; cuid15734 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Women's Swimming, 1959; cuid15735 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- RG 41.15: Diving, cuid15736
  Series 41.13 is comprised of the records of the Diving Team.
- RG 41.17: Volleyball, cuid15737
  Series 41.17 is comprised of the records of the Volleyball Team.
  - #6 WVLB/MVLB (00-01), undated; cuid15833 (Box 91, Cassette rg41_cuid15833)
  - WVLB/MVCC/WXCC/MSOC/WSOC/MFEN/WFEN/DANCE/MBBL/FENC, 2001-2002; 2018-02; cuid470 (Box 91, Cassette cuid470, Box Shared University Archives 118, Item 37)
    Original format: Hi8mm, Duration: 105 min., Color, Sound
    Housing Annotations
    WVLB vs Pace: 9/19/01 MXCC/WXCC 9/22/01 NYU Invite MSOC WSOC Fencing (M/W) Dance MBBL Fencing (M/W)
  - MTEN, MVLB vs Juniata Elva, 2002-04; cuid15831 (Box 91, Cassette rg41_cuid15831)
    Original format: Hi8mm, Duration: 120 min.
- RG 41.18: Wrestling
  History of Wrestling at NYU
  Wrestling became a varsity sport at NYU in 1934 under the direction of Olympian Charles Cranford. Interest declined the following season and the wrestling program went on hiatus until 1939. In the 1970s the NYU wrestlers topped the Metropolitan and Eastern rankings. The wrestling team competes today at the Division III level of the NCAA. They are a member of the University Athletic Association (UAA) Conference.
  Series 41.13 is comprised of the records of the Wrestling Team.
  - Varsity Wrestling, 1946-1947; cuid15738 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Wrestling Student Athlete Registration Cards, 1985-1986; cuid15830 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted due to FERPA regulations.
  - NYU Wrestling Home Match, 7 February 2004; 2018-02; cuid468 (Box 91, Cassette rg41_cuid468, Box Shared University Archives 118, Item 35)
- RG 41.19: Softball, cuid15739
  Series 41.13 is comprised of the records of the Softball Team.
- RG 41.20: Bowling
  History of Bowling at NYU
  NYU briefly had an all-female bowling team that competed during the 1940s and 1950s.
  Series 41.13 is comprised of the records of the Bowling Team.
  - Women's Bowling, 1945-1947; cuid15740 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- RG 41.21: Riflery
  History of Riflery at NYU
  Riflery was brought back to NYU in 1929 after having been dissolved years earlier. The team practiced at ranges on the University Heights campus and had great successes during the 1930s. In 1931 the freshmen team was named the national intercollegiate champion. Riflery is no longer a competitive sport at NYU.
  Series 41.13 is comprised of the records of the Riflery Team.
  - Varsity Rifle, 1946-1947; cuid15741 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- RG 41.22: Field Hockey
  History of Field Hockey at NYU
  The NYU field hockey team played its first games in the 1924 season. This varsity team practiced at Central Park and Prospect Park. In 1931 the team played a game on the Ohio Field at University Heights, becoming the first female team to play on this field. Field hockey is no longer a competitive sport at NYU.
  Series 41.13 is comprised of the records of the Field Hockey Team.
  - Women's Field Hockey, 1945-1947; cuid15742 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Unprocessed Materials, cuid15783 (Box 232, Box 233, Box 234, Box 235, Box 237, Box 269)